<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[joelcasey.com]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[joelcasey.com]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2016 00:16:03 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="undefinedrss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Walk In Faith]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>A Walk In Faith</h1><p>To you the reader–experiencing life is one thing; to have the opportunity to share those experiences is quite another. 	May the words in this book serve as a beacon of light and inspiration. May they be a gentle reminder that love is always with us and within us, even in the times when we lose all hope and our faith is challenged beyond our beliefs. Love is always there. Love is constant, eternal, abiding in and through all forms. Though it may be obscured from our awareness at times, Love Is. 	Thank you in advance for allowing me the chance to express my experiences of living by faith and trusting in a Supreme Intelligence from which all things are made, and which, in its original state permeates, penetrates and fills the interspaces of the universe.   	We use the word God, Father, Father/Mother, Creative Intelligence, in an attempt to describe the indescribable One Being, which is within, without, and Is all things. 	Even though you will see that my faith was pushed to the limit at times and trust was nearly exhausted, you will also see that faith did, and does work… always. And like always, our perceived threats and feelings of separation from our Source are unknowingly self-imposed. 	I invite you to join me now as our journey of A Walk In Faith unfolds…</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/89c1977c-2f7c-416a-9860-c10279d53a46.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>undefinedc86544f4-2760-44f9-84ef-a9cfd40e39ed/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c86544f4-2760-44f9-84ef-a9cfd40e39ed</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2016 00:16:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>